- What's up?
(Leonard:)You ever make it to the dentist?
Not necessary. I found a service that'll send
a van to your house for a teeth cleaning.
(Sheldon:)Mostly they cater to dogs...
(Sheldon:)...but the fellow on the phone
seemed to have an open mind.
(Leonard:)All right, Sheldon, if you need me
to take you to the dentist, I will take you.
(Sheldon:)Are you suggesting
that you've come to your senses...
...and wish to reestablish the benefits
that stem from the Roommate Agreement?
Absolutely. If you admit you're a 30-year-old
man incapable of functioning on his own.
(Raj:)Ooh. Sock Mouth's got him on the ropes.
(Sheldon:)I will admit nothing of the sort.
And now, if you'll excuse me...
(Sheldon:)...I have to call my dentist and see if I can
get my hair shampooed and nails clipped.